I died. [laughter] Okay, it's working.
Joe wanted me to analyze these doodads,
so I'm going to be doing it today.
>> Can I tell you what I've been told they
are?
>> Yeah.
>> These came out of Mexico, were found in
buried substrata with charcoal dated
[music] around 4,000 years. We don't
know exactly what they are. When you
take them and connect them properly,
they only go one way.
When properly oriented,
>> Mhm.
>> they make light. A lot of people think
that they have batteries in there and
other things, but I don't know what it
is. I'd think some type of pio electric
or frequency energy. Do they look
authentic to [music] you? Do they look
like reproductions? What do you think,
Parker?
>> Honest opinion, these do look like
reproductions of something. I have an
Aztec, like one of those heads, you
know, they're made out of the same
material, but it's a reproduction. And
then inside of here, I believe there is
like a little LED. See, you can see
where they mounted it with some kind of
concrete paste. This is a crystal. They
had to mount it there uh with some kind
of concrete paste. And then the
terminals at the bottom connect to that
LED that's inside of there.
>> It almost [music] looks like this one
has been fused in the middle.
>> Yes. Very heavy.
>> Abnormally heavier than So there's
something inside of that such as a
battery or something.
>> What do you have here? And how are you
going to test this? I have an electrical
measure. Batteries produce direct
current. If that's anything to do with a
frequency, there will be alternating
current. If it's direct current, we know
there's a battery in there. You would
need a rectifier to rectify the
alternating current to make it direct
current. This where you take the waves
and you make a full wave.
>> Do you have an X-ray machine?
>> I do. Right over here.
>> We're going to theorize and then we'll
X-ray these things.
>> So, we're going to test the voltage in
it first. I assume it shall be around 9
volts of direct current.
>> So, yep, it's 8.29. [music]
Let me cut it on AC and see if we get
anything. We have nothing right there.
Touch it again. [music] Just take it
off.
>> Just touch it's on.
>> When you first touch it, it goes to 1.4
2.1.
It's reading a little bit of AC.
Describe that phenomenon for me, Parker.
>> It's making alternating current
>> just from you touching it.
>> Yeah.
>> Just a static type charge.
>> I'm making a frequency by doing this.
Now, if I hold it on there, that would
be direct current. It doesn't register.
So, it wants direct current. Here are
the copper leads.
We have nothing.
>> Correct.
>> Let's check the resistance cuz that's
how we'll find out if there's
>> is there filament in there or something,
right?
>> We have any ohms.
>> No. If there was a filament in there
running, it would [music] it would out
>> resistance between the fil. It's
probably LED light emmitting diode. That
means it can flow one way.
>> They are kind of baffling, aren't they?
>> Mhm.
>> This is putting out voltage, but this is
not. I'm going to go back to my DC. See
if I can get in there. No, I can't get
in there cuz it'll [music] it'll break
it.
>> Oh, and we didn't do the torch yet. So,
this one I was testing it a little bit.
It produces roughly 6 volt from these
terminals right here.
>> There you go. So, it keeps dying out
now. There you go. 6 and 1/2 [music]
6.4.
>> If you take metal and short these one
sec, it's lighting up when I short
these. Now,
>> take it off. Now, touch it again.
So, he just took grounded it out with a
screwdriver.
>> Makes me think there's like a battery
built into this with an LED and
[clears throat] solar panels.
>> And I don't know how you charge [music]
this
>> through the
>> Just let the crystals stay in the sun.
>> Well, there's a solar panel under the
crystal.
>> Well, we'll find out in the X-ray, won't
we?
>> It's not voltage. It's continuity. No
voltage. See,
>> let me check AC real quick. See, it's
not creating any AC there. But you can
have continuity.
>> Let's hear it. Let's hear it.
>> And you show these.
>> Stone is not conductive.
>> Oh, but this metal strip is.
>> And now if you look right there, I don't
see how it's connected.
>> Under the stone.
>> This is the screwdriver in this case.
>> I think the moment of truth will be
x-raying these things.
>> Mhm.
>> Cuz if there's a battery in here
>> we know we have a fraud. What do you
think? If there's no battery in here,
>> possibly solar power. I don't know.
>> So, if if there's no battery in here, we
both going to be scratching our heads
some more. How do you X-ray this thing?
What do you use?
>> The odds machine from the 1930s. And I'm
going to use this uh Desmar A212 that my
friend Griffin Jeep Brock made.
>> Do we need to turn this light off?
>> Yeah. So, I'm going to connect this to
this coil. And this would work better
with X-ray film.
>> Mhm.
>> Glad I don't have any.
>> Am I allowed to touch your light switch?
>> [laughter]
>> Am I allowed to touch your shoulder?
>> Your butt?
>> No.
>> I'm Br. No.
>> Br. Bruh.
>> Br. Okay, let me test this.
>> Hold [laughter] on. Okay, it's working.
>> Joe, I need you to get out of my way. I
better come over here.
>> I need to concentrate. Okay, [laughter]
are we ready? Okay.
[music]
If there was a battery in there.
>> Well, it's probably [music]
>> Let's check that little one.
>> Something about this feels dangerous.
How bad did it hurt?
>> The ozone is intense.
>> Look how hot.
>> Uh, yeah. I wonder why. You just made
lightning in here and wonder. [laughter]
Am I allowed to pick this up?
>> No. Please. Reminds me of Lily. You know
how she'd say no.
Lily Kate fells, I miss you, baby.
[music] I'm thinking about you and Mikey
all the time.
>> Parker, lightning makes heat. I need to
get a dentist or [music] a doctor with a
private practice to x-ray these things.
>> I just need some X-ray film and an X-ray
cassette and I could X-ray [music]
things up to 20 ft away through walls
and stuff.
>> These things haven't been in the sun in
months and [music] it still lights up.
So, if there was a battery in there,
just off the weight, how big could it
be? That's not very heavy. Batteries are
extremely heavy. I've been totally
>> So, how long would a 9volt battery last
with no charge?
>> I see the LED in here.
>> I don't see an LED. I just see crystal.
>> It's like right
>> Let me see.
>> There. You can only see the top of it.
>> I see I see that
>> that top of that.
>> That's just
>> It's like a dome shape in there.
>> It's a tiny [music] little thing. I
think it's part of the crystal. You can
see that. There's a There's a bunch of
them. We need an X-ray. Yeah,
>> cuz
>> a better X-ray.
>> These things are so puzzling, man. I've
spent hours trying to figure out how
they work. If I can figure out how this
works,
>> then we can make energy out of rocks.
Who do I have to take these to?
>> I get them X-ray better.
>> You see how they're both the same
[music] color crystal, but they put out
a gold light and a white light.
Symbolizes the sun and [music] the moon.
Also kind of a halo imagery going on.
Don't those look kind of like wiring
diagrams to you? a 120 leg, you have hot
neutral ground. That's what I keep
wondering on things like this. What kind
of tool did they make this with? If we
split one open, we could tell. [music]
Did you see the back of this thing?
>> Yeah.
>> If they were making fakes of these, how
much do you think it cost to produce one
of these? Cuz if this was poured in a
mold, that's not a mold, though. Look,
you can see the pores in the rock. It's
It's unfinished right there. harvesting
electricity for PZ electric purposes, it
would have to use alternating current
because that builds the frequency to
strike the P the crystal at the right
frequency to emit light.
>> If there's no battery in this, then
what?
>> Mhm. [snorts] I mean, there's some kind
of power source in there.
>> Yes, I know. That's what I'm trying to
find out.
>> If it's not a battery, could possibly be
capacitors or something.
Parker, I've taken these to Julian. I
brought these to [music] you. And none
of us can come up with a conclusive
answer. And that's the thing. [music]
They're so mindboggling. It's easier to
just say they're fake. But I saw a lot
of fake down there, right? And then
I saw stuff like this that was like,
>> wait a minute. It's almost like whoever
made these [music] is just toying with
us with the DC energy. That is kind of
an outlier. You know, I was expecting to
see a little bit of AC current. I think
these things are trying to tell [music]
us a story. You know, if you think about
all the symbolism in the Freemason
house, we have seven there, seven
worlds. We're living in the [music]
eighth now,
>> a third eye. You see, they all have a
third eye. They have the sun, the moon,
they have orbs, four fingers, [music]
>> just like the Egyptian sarcophaguses,
>> and he's sitting here placed. There's
almost another face here, and lots of
triangles with the eye. Vesica Pisces
symbols and things of that nature. I
would love for there to be a battery in
here. You know why? It'd be a much
neater explanation. [music]
Cuz if there's no battery in here, we're
still back at square zero. If I could
figure out that there's a battery in
here, I could just toss these and say
[music] these are fakes. But I
don't think there's a battery in here
just because I don't see where the hell
they put one in here. Now, I could see
one being under here with all that, but
I also don't know how the hell it would
charge. [music] We've had these things
lit up and different people walked in
the room and they'd shut off. And then
there was another one in Mexico that
would not [music] cut on when you were
recording it. I thought I was going to
get to go to sleep tonight, Parker.
Dude, but thank you, homie. You know,
you you and Julian are some of my best
homies cuz y'all are weird energy bros.
I thought I was going to get to the
bottom of this. Not tonight.
Thank you for [music] using your
lightning x-ray machine in your kitchen
and for welcoming your home, homie.
Always a good time, dude. What are we
going to do next?
>> We got a ghost.
>> Yeah. Let's go with some ghosts.